Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design,Corcoran Gallery of Art education department records 1961-2010 COR0006.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Tours, interns, publicity files [2016 processing project], 1971-2000; Series 21
  - Shruti Adhar, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Emily Johnson, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Internship Grants, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Birthday Parties General, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Birthday Party - Alexandra Levy, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Birthday Party - Soraya Jaran, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Emma Sayre, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Birthday Party Reardon, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Alexander Levy 2000 Birthday Party, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Levy Birthday 2001 Sat. Oct. 13, 2001 October 13; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Family Progs 1997-1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Family Progs 1998-1999, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Still Life - or is it Moving Sunday 2:30pm, 1998 October 25; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Gobble up your Artwork Sunday 2:30pm, 1998 November 22; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Literature Comes to Life Sunday 2:30pm, 1998 November 8; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Magical Marvelous Holidays Sunday 2:30pm, 1998 December 13; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Fables, Folktales, Myths Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 January 24; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - I Made It Out of Clay Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 January 10; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - For the Love of Art 1999 Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 February 14; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Hop to it Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 February 28; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Color Power Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 March 28; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Tell Me A Story Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 April 11-; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Musical Pictures Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 April 25; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Picture This for Mother's Day Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 May 9; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Kites-A-Flying Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 May 23; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Jug Band Basics Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 June 6; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Father's Day: Lost and Found Sunday 2:30pm, 1999 June 20; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Family Programs 1999-2000, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Sunday Traditions The Land That I Love, 1999 October 10; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - SundayTraditions Flags Around the World, 1999 October 24; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - Sunday Traditions Painting Comes to Life, 1999 November 7; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - CANCELED Sunday Traditions Thanksgiving Feast, 1999 November 21; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Sunday Traditions Magical Holiday Treat, 1999 December 19; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Sunday Traditions What's in a Rock?, 1999 Decmeber 5; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - Sunday Traditions Puppets on Parade, 2000 January 9; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - Sunday Traditions Key of Life, 2000 January 23; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 106)
  - Sunday Traditions From the Heart, 2000 February 6; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 107)
  - Sunday Traditions Listen to the Beat of the Drums, 2000 February 27; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 108)
  - Sunday Traditions Sculpt with Paper, 2000 March 26; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 109)
  - Sunday Traditions Mother Earth, 2000 March 12; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 110)
  - Sunday Traditions Hare, Hare Everywhere, 2000 April 16; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 111)
  - Sunday Traditions Spring in the Art, 2000 April 30; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 112)
  - Sunday Traditions Moms in Art, 2000 May 14; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 113)
  - Sunday Traditions Grandmother's Attic, 2000 May 21; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 114)
  - Sunday Traditions Sidewalks Come to Life, 2000 June 4; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 115)
  - Sunday Traditions Mural, Mural on the Wall, 2000 June 18; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 116)
  - 2000-2001 Family Program, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 117)
  - Sunday Traditions Express Yourself, 2000 October 1-; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 118)
  - Sunday Traditions Back to the Future, 2000 October 15; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 119)
  - Sunday Traditions Growl! Roar! Grrr!, 2000 October 29; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 120)
  - Sunday Traditions Movve to the Beat of the Art, 2000 November 12; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 121)
  - Sunday Traditions Play it Again, Sam, 2000 November 19; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 122)
  - Sunday Traditions Winter Holiday Festival, 2000 December 10; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 123)
  - Sunday Traditions Mosaic Magic, 2000 December 3; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 124)
  - Sunday Traditions Abstract, In Fact!, 2001 January 7; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - Sunday Traditions Mix It Up, 2001 January 21; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - Sunday Traditions Shape Up with Art, 2001 February 25; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - Sunday Traditions Edible Art, 2001 March 4; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 128)
  - Sunday Traditions Art in Motion, 2001 March 18; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 129)
  - Sunday Traditions April Fools!, 2001 April 1; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 130)
  - Sunday Traditions Hanging Around, 2001 April 22; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 131)
  - Sunday Traditions All Bound Up, 2001 May 6; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 132)
  - Sunday Traditions Cowboy Art, 2001 May 20; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 133)
  - Sunday Traditions Lights, Camera, Action!, 2001 June 3; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 134)
  - Sunday Traditions Surreal Summer Stories, 2001 June 24; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 135)
  - Adult Tour Techniques, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Aesthetics, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Tour Outlines, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Landscape, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - [American Genre], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Tour Preparation (Empty), Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Silent Subjects (Empty), Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Face to Face, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Teaching Art to Novices, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Look Again, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - The Painted Sketch, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Tour Stats, 1980-1981; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Tour Statistics, 1982-1983; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Estimate to Reprint Storybrook, 1989 March; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Senior Outreach, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Tours/Schools, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Tour Techniques, Etc., Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Senior Outreach Info: Lists, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - [The Art of Aging], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - For High Schools Only, 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Docent Program/Funding Proposal, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Internships, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - [Internships], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - High School Interns, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - [Internship Training], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - [Applications], 1990-1992; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - [Possible Intern Projects], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - [Intern Handbook], 1994; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Summer Internship Program, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - GWU Interns, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Internship, 1994; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - GW Museum Education, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Museum Studies, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Museum Careers, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - [Museum Education Packets], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Lists, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - DC Cultural Consortium, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - List Community Advisory Board CGA 94, 1994; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Community Advisory Board Directory, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Community Relations, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - School Children Membership, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Programs!, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Friends Program, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Adult Programs Survey, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Weekend Program Supevisor, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Appalachian Lab, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Education Programs, 1996; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - [Associated Writing Programs], Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Janet Solinger/Special Projects, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Writers (Museum Ed)/Consultants, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Boiler Plate Information/Examples, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Brochure, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Tour Brochure, Circa 1996-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - School Tour Poster, 1997-1998; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - School Tour Poster, 1996-1997; Series 21 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Information/Research on Various Art/Artists, Undated; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Loose Docent Information, Undated; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Loose Publication Bibliography, Undated; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Loose Docent Training Information, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Docent: Background, Techniques, Clark Collection, American Collection, Look Again, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Docents: Face to Face, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Docents: Architecture is Elementary, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Docents: European Collection Primary Views, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Docents: Fables, Folktales, Myths and Sculpture, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 70, Folder 9)